<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>city2jungle</title>
    <link>https://100trillion.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on city2jungle</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>ko-kr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 20:36:23 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://100trillion.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>From concrete jungle to green oasis: the need for more natural spaces in seoul</title>
      <link>https://100trillion.github.io/posts/concrete-jungle-green-oasis-natural-spaces-seoul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 20:36:23 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://100trillion.github.io/posts/concrete-jungle-green-oasis-natural-spaces-seoul/</guid>
      <description>In my previous blog post, I discussed the importance of green spaces in cities and why it is crucial for cities to prioritize their creation and maintenance. However, many cities around the world, including Seoul, are facing a shortage of green spaces, which has significant implications for the health and well-being of urban residents.
Seoul is the capital city of South Korea and home to over 10 million people. While the city has made significant progress in recent years towards becoming more sustainable, the lack of green spaces remains a major challenge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The importance of green spaces in cities</title>
      <link>https://100trillion.github.io/posts/the-importance-of-green-spaces-in-cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Apr 2023 18:38:37 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://100trillion.github.io/posts/the-importance-of-green-spaces-in-cities/</guid>
      <description>Urbanization is on the rise, and as cities become more densely populated, the need for green spaces has become increasingly apparent. Green spaces are defined as parks, gardens, and other areas of natural vegetation that provide a multitude of benefits to urban areas. In this blog post, we will explore the importance of green spaces and why cities should prioritize their creation and maintenance.
Environmental benefits One of the primary benefits of green spaces is their positive impact on the environment.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
